A Guide to the Dr. Richard Zallen Papers, 1957-2009
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series XIII: Correspondence
  - Steve Groves [SHG], 1970-2006 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - B.I. Halperin, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Tim Hayes, 1978-1996 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Alan Heeger, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Heinz Henisch, 1968-2006 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Dudley Herschback, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Jorge Hirsch, 2005 (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Diane Hoffman, 1984-2002 (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Mark Holtz (1 of 2), 1982-2006 (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Mark Holtz (2 of 2 ), 1982-2006 (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Puru Jena, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Ai‐Lien Jung, China (1986), 1981-1988 (Box-folder 20:12)
  - Marc Kastner, 1972-1972 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Bob Knox / RSK / Symmetry, Tunneling, 1970-2007 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Imants Lauks, 1982-2006 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Yi‐Bai Li, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Cliff Lilly, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Gerry Lucovsky, 1965-2000 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Benoit Mandelbrot, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Richard Martin, 1971-1997 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - E‐mail Correspondence with Richard Martin, et al. Vis‐à‐vis IR Activity in Elemental Crystals, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Scott Massie, 1990-2006 (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Jim McGroddy, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 21:11)
  - Laurie McNeil, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 21:12)
  - Mona Moret, 1994-2006 (Box-folder 21:13)
  - Si Moss, 1973-2004 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Neville Mott, 1968-1996 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Stan and Iris Ovshinsky, 1981-2006 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Damodar Pai, Damodar Pai (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Bill Paul (1 of 3), 1959-2005 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Bill Paul (2 of 3), 1959-2005 (Folder 22:6)
  - Bill Paul (3 of 3), 1959-2005 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - WP's Sixtieth Birthday Party in Las Vegas (1986), 1964-1986 (Box-folder 22:8)
  - George Pake, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 22:9)
  - WP Nominations: NAS, Mott Medal, Buckley Prize, 1988-2001 (Box-folder 22:10)
  - WP Bridgman‐medal Attempts, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 22:11)
  - Stuart Pawley, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Rudolf Peieris, 1986-1971 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Erik Pell, 1983-2002 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Correspondence with Jim Phillips, 1969-2004 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Zoran Popovic, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Ilan Riess, 1972-2002 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Nick Rivier (Sep 12 1991), 1980-1997 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Gareth Roberts [G2], 1970- 2005 (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Bill Salaneck, 1983-2006 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Carl Sagan, 1975 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Dror Sarid, 1976-1994 (Box-folder 23:11)
  - Harvey Scher, 1978-2006 (Box-folder 23:12)
  - Brian Schwartz, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 23:13)
  - Phil Schmid, 1974-1996 (Box-folder 23:14)
  - Boris Shapiro, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Bea Shube, n.d. (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Alf Siochi, 1988-2006 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Stu Solin / Visits: Xerox (1969, 1967), Virginia Tech (1986, 2006), 1968-2006 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Wantana Songprakob [Nui], 1995-2006 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Walter Spear, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Tony Stradling, 1989-2003 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Jan Tauc (folder 1 of 3), 1962-2002 (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Jan Tauc (folder 2 of 3), 1962-2002 (Box-folder 24:9)
  - Jan Tauc (folder 3 of 3), 1962-2002 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Craig Taylor, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Mike Thorpe, 1983-2006 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - David Thouless, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Jim Tsang, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Dave Tsu, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Ray Tsu, 1970-2002 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Sathan Vijarnwannaluck ["Daeng"], 1995-2004 (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Denis Weaire, 1983-2005 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Bernie Weinstein (folder 1 of 2), 1973-2006 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Bernie Weinstein (folder 2 of 2), 1973-2006 (Box-folder 25:11)
  - Gerhard Weiser, 1971-1990 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Barbara Wilson, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Adrian Wright, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - M. K. Wu / high Te, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - A. D. Yoffe, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 26:5)
- Series IX: Zallen Research Materials: Optical Properties / Phonons / Elemental Crystals / Layer Crystals / Pressure‐Raman / Percolation
  - Percolation Lectures, Xerox (1973, 1977), 1973-1977 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Polychromatic Percolation (1976-1977), 1970-1978 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Percolation Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - PCPC Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - Polychromatic Percolation Color VUE Graphs and Drawings, n.d. (Box-folder 26:10)
  - PCPC Flat Plates & Originals, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 26:11)
  - Percolation, 1977 (Box-folder 26:12)
  - Percolation Originals for Stat Phys Slides, 1977 (Box-folder 26:13)
  - PCPC, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 26:14)
  - Harvey's Sec. (3) of 25, 1971 (Box-folder 26:15)
  - Percolation Figures and Flat Plates, 1970 (Box-folder 26:16)
  - Zallen and Scher Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 26:17)
  - Figures / Zallen & Scher, 1971 (Box-folder 26:18)
  - Z & S Percolation Outlines, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 26 folder 19)
  - PBI2/2H→?/ Pressure‐Inducted Transition [Notes from Open Desk File January 1980] (Box-folder 26:20)
  - PbI2 Under Pressure [Unpublished] 1975-1985 (Box-folder 26:21)
  - Correspondence / 2H→4H PbI2 Paper, 1975 (Box-folder 26:22)
  - Sound‐Velocity Accordion, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 26:23)
  - As4S4 & S4N4 n.d. (Box-folder 26:24)
  - Zallen's Law; γ ~ 1/ω2, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - As4S4/S4N4 Figures and Drawings, n.d. (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Correspondence: Influence of Pressure & Temperature on Phonons in As4S4 & S4N4, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Sulfur Optical Properties Paper [EDZ], 1976 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - ZB Review (≈1974), 1973-1985 (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Correspondence: Zallen and Blossey Review on Arsenic Chalcogenide Layer Crystals, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Correspondence: Zallen & Conwell Libron Paper, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Notes on Simple Spring Model, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Vibrational Reduced Mass μ, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 27:9)
  - RL modes (1974), 1969-1975 (Box-folder 27:10)
  - Pressure‐Raman Paper Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 27:11)
  - Pressure‐Raman (1974), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 27:12)
  - Drawings: Phonons in Two‐Dimensional Solids, 1976 (Box-folder 27:13)
  - Pyrene & Pressure‐Raman Figures II, n.d. (Box-folder 27:14)
  - Pressure‐Raman Paper Figures, n.d. (Box-folder 27:15)
  - Stuttgart / Glossy Prints & Flat Plates [to size], 1974 (Box-folder 27:16)
  - Stuttgart Paper 16 D 06 Originals, 1974 (Box-folder 27:17)
  - Pressure‐Raman & Rigid Layer Figures, 1974 (Box-folder 27:18)
  - Talk on Optical Properties of Amorphous and Molecular Solids (March 1973), 1973 (Box-folder 27:19)
  - Solid State Spectroscopy / One Page Review of Accomplishments (Jan 28 1974), 1974-1977 (Box-folder 27:20)
  - Sb2S3 / Infrared & UV Spectra Flat Plate Set 1 [unpublished], n.d. (Box-folder 27:21)
  - Sb2S3 Interband & Lattice Spectra [unpublished] (1971), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 27:22)
  - 2 Figures: Rigid Layer Modes in Chalcogenide Crystals: As2Se3, n.d. (Box-folder 27:23)
  - c‐ & a‐ As2S3 XPS, 1976 (Box-folder 27:24)
  - Amorphous As2S3 & A2Se3 Absorption Edges, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 27:25)
  - Electronic Structure of Crystalline and Amorphous As2S3 & As 2Se3, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 27:26)
  - R(h2), @ 10°K; c‐As2S3 & c‐As2Se3, n.d. (Box-folder 27:27)
  - ZDEX Correspondence (1971), 1968-1976 (Box-folder 27:28)
  - Diperiodic Groups Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box-folder 27:29)
  - As2Se3‐As2Se3 / Latt. Vib. Flat Plates 2, n.d. (Box-folder 27:30)
  - e* (As2S3), 1969-1979 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - e*, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - As2S3 & As2Se3 average ν, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 28:3)
  - ZSW (1971), 1967-1976 (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Amorphous Ge (1968-1969), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Se Review / Flat Plates, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Se Review, 1970 (Box-folder 28:7)
  - Figures for Se Review, n.d. (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Se Review‐Spare Flat Plates, n.d. (Box-folder 28:9)
  - Drawings for Slides: Reststrahlen in Elemental Crystals, n.d. (Box-folder 28:10)
  - Outlines: Z & CZ, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:11)
  - Correspondence about Z & CZ, 1968 (Box-folder 28:12)
  - 1968 Theory Paper / IR Modes in Elemental Crystals, 1967-1993
  - Zallen and Chen, Moscow Conference, 1968 1968 (Box-folder 28:14)
  - 1 Set of Good Flat Plates and Glossy Prints / Z & CZ, n.d. (Box-folder 28:15)
  - Spare Flat Plate Copies for Z & CZ (1968), 1968 (Box-folder 28:16)
  - Shell‐Model Notes, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:17)
  - Group Theory for D3? Dynamical Matrix / NNN Models for A2 Modes (9/21‐10/2/1967), 1967 (Box-folder 28:18)
  - CZ (10/15‐12/14/1967), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:19)
  - D34, n.d. (Box-folder 28:20)
  - Coulomb Interaction; IC's Notes from BH / Kellermann, 1940-1969 (Box-folder 28:21)
  - Chen & Zallen (10/18/1967‐2/20/1968), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:22)
  - HgS Thermal Modulation / RX Notes, Calculations, & Drawings: Abkowitz, Pfister, & Zallen, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 28:23)
  - HgS Thermal Modulation: Abkowitz, Pfister, & Zallen, n.d. (Box-folder 28:24)
  - Semiconductor‐Semimetal Transitions by Alloying, 1970 (Box-folder 28:25)
  - Semi Metals, 1957-1970 (Box-folder 28:26)
  - HgSe (1997), 1970-1997 (Box-folder 28:27)
  - β‐HgS Figures for Paper, n.d. (Box-folder 28:28)
  - β‐HgS / n, m*, τ, 1970-1998 (Box-folder 28:29)
  - β‐HgS Analyses for Impurities, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 28:30)
  - β‐HgS Talk, 1970 (Box-folder 28:31)
  - β‐HgS, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - β‐HgS Figures, n.d. (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Unpublished HgS UV, 1979 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Edge Reflectivity Luminescence: HgS, 1967 (Box-folder 29:4)
  - HgS Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - HgS Flat Plates [set 2], 1969 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - HgS Original Draft, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Madelung Energy, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 29:8)
  - HgS Mode Models, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 29:9)
  - HgS IR‐R Selection‐Rule Notes, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 29:10)
  - HgS Edge, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 29:11)
  - α‐HgS / Crystal Growth, Preparation, 1970-1994 (Box-folder 29:12)
  - HgS a‐c′ Planar Projection, 1969 (Box-folder 29:13)
  - HgS Crystal Structure, 1969 (Box-folder 29:14)
  - E2 Sum Rule: Ehrenreich Nozièers & Pines Pippard, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 29:15)
  - RZ Notes on Optical Properties, 1962 (Box-folder 29:16)
  - Smith / NATO Lectures, Gent Belgium (1962), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 29:17)
  - Warschauer, 1960 (Box-folder 29:18)
- Series X: Zallen Research Materials 1979-2005: nanocrystalline GaAs & AlO(OH) / 1994 elemental crystals / TiO2 / GaAS:C and Global information: CV / mailing list / experimental methods/optical properties notes
  - Mailing Lists, 1980-1994 (Box-folder 29:19)
  - CV, 1970-2009 (Box-folder 29:20)
  - RZ Refereeing Reports [some of them], 1975-2005 (Box-folder 29:21)
  - Survey Absorption Spectrum [Bink original], 1967-1968 (Box-folder 29:22)
  - T(hν)‐Absorption Edge Procedure & Thickness from Interference Fringes, 1962-1996 (Box-folder 29:23)
  - Notes on the Optical Properties of Metals (1 of 2), 1960-2002 (Box-folder 29:24)
  - Optical Properties, etc (folder 2 of 2), 1957-2002 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - s→p Energy Spacings & Bonding, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - External Optics for Vis‐UV Spectrometer (≈1966), 1966 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Optical Spectrometer Visible / Ultraviolet, 1965-1996 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Miscellaneous Raman‐Lab Notes, 1975-2004 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Miscellaneous Experimental, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Infrared Lab, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Photomultipliers, 2001 (Box-folder 30:8)
  - Spectrometers, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 30:9)
  - Etches, 1966 (Box-folder 30:10)
  - Samples Sent Out, 1974-2004 (Box-folder 30:11)
  - Brookite‐TiO2 Paper (1996-2005), 1968-2005 (Box-folder 30:12)
  - GaAs:C, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 30:13)
  - SBT Versus Temp / Kamba et al. [Kamba, Petzelt, Moret, Garg, Barber, Zallen], 1999-2002 (Box-folder 30:14)
  - e* [anatase] (1996), 1961-1996 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Anatase-TiO2 Paper, 1996 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - SrBiTa2O9 [mostly 1997], 1995-1997 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - SBT IR Work / MZNJD Paper, 1997 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Analysis for Number of IR and Raman Modes / SBT (1997), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Moret Invention Disclosure on Thin‐Film Deposition, 1996 (Box-folder 31:6)
  - RZ Contribution to Encyclopaedia Britannica (1993-1994), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 31:7)
  - 1994 Theory Paper / IR Modes In Elemental Crystals, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Correspondence: ZMN, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Figure 1 [Originals], 1993 (Box-folder 31:10)
  - Solid H2 (mostly 1993), 1968-1997 (Box-folder 31:11)
  - CD Figures Back from Physics Review (1993), 1992-1993 (Box-folder 31:12)
  - Calvin Doss / Sol‐Gel Alumina AlO(OH), 1990-1993 (Box-folder 31:13)
  - Taucschrift Paper, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 31:14)
  - FZ Figures, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 31:15)
  - FZ‐MRS Short Paper (1988), 1988-1993 (Box-folder 31:16)
  - HZBM Figures, 1987 (Box-folder 31:17)
  - Miscellaneous GaAs, 1988-2002 (Box-folder 31:18)
  - NSF Referees on BDZ, 1988 (Box-folder 31:19)
  - Work with Texas Instruments / GaAs (1985-1986), 1985-1989 (Box-folder 31:20)
  - HZGS / GaAs / Journal of Applied Physics Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 31:21)
  - Higher‐dimensional Sphere Packings Notes & Calculations (1985), 1976-1985 (Box-folder 31:22)
  - Paper for Texas A&M (September 1986), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 31:23)
  - Originals for VUE‐Graphs / Miscellaneous Amorphous, n.d. (Box-folder 31:24)
  - Semiconductor Handbook [WP] Correspondence, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - GeS2 Unpublished Raman Figures (work done ≈ 1982), 1986-1989 (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Grenoble Figures, n.d. (Box-folder 32:3)
  - GeS2 Article / Linguini, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Figures for Crystal Structures, 1979 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Graph for the Diamond Structure, 1981 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Z.W: Local Topography & Geometry [Table III], 1979-1981 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Crystal Structures Handwritten Manuscript, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Distribution of Structures / Background Material for Figure 1, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Crystal Structures Tables, 1979 (Box-folder 32:10)
  - RZ Review of the Book Ordering in Two Dimensions, 1981 (Box-folder 32:11)
  - Statphys Review, n.d. (Box-folder 32:12)
  - (Cl2)2 Herschbach; Beswick & Jertner, 1979-1994 (Box-folder 32:14)
  - Annals of the Israel Physical Society Volume 5 (1983), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 32:15)
  - Pressure‐Raman Effects in Covalent and Molecular Solids by B. A. Weinstein and R. Zallen, n.d. (Box-folder 32:16)
  - W & Z Springer Review, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 32:17)
  - Stochastic Geometry: Aspects of Amorphous Solids, c. 1979 (Box-folder 32:18)
  - Stochastic Geometry Photostats back from North Holland, n.d. (Box-folder 32:19)
  - Correspondence Concerning Stochastic Geometry..., 1978-1987 (Box-folder 32:20)
- Series XI: Material for the Physics of Amorphous Solids and the Book in Several Editions
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. New York: John Wiley & Sons, 1983. (Box-folder 32:21)
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. New York: John Wiley & Sons, 1998. (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. [Chinese Translation], Beijing: Beijing University Press, 1998. (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. [Hardcover Edition] New York: John Wiley & Sons, 1983. (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. [Polish Translation] Warszawa: Wydawnictwo Naukowe PWN, 1994. (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Zallen, Richard. The Physics of Amorphous Solids. Weinheim: Wiley-VCH, 2004. (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Manuscript Index for The Physics of Amorphous Solids, 1983 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Fundamentals of Amorphous Semiconductors. Washington, DC: National Academy of Sciences, 1972. (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Structural Model for Amorphous Silicon and Germanium by D. E. Polk for the Office of Naval Research, 1970 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - References, Captions, and Hand Insertions, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Correspondence about Book (1988-1989), 1985-1998 (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Bea Shube / Correspondence about RZ Book (folder 1 of 2), 1975-1988 (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Bea Shube / Correspondence about RZ Book (folder 2 of 2), 1975-1988 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Drafts‐Chapter One, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Drafts‐Chapter Two, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 34:6)
    Entitled Chapter Two on folder but numbering indicates folder represents original Chapter One.
  - Drafts‐Chapter Three, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 34:7)
    Entitled Chapter Three on folder but numbering indicates folder represents original Chapter Four.
  - Drafts‐Percolation Chapter Four, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 35:1)
    Entitled Chapter Four on folder but numbering indicates folder represents original Chapter Five.
  - Drafts‐Chapter Five, 1982 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Drafts‐Chapter Six, 1982 (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Chapter One‐Ink Originals, 1981 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Chapter Two‐Ink Originals, 1982 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Chapter Three‐Ink Originals, n.d. (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Chapter Four‐Percolation Ink Originals, 1981 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Chapter Five‐Ink Originals, n.d. (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Chapter Six‐Ink Originals, n.d. (Box-folder 35:9)
  - Stochastic Geometry Ink Originals, n.d. (Box-folder 35:10)
  - Flyers‐The Physics of Amorphous Solids, 1983 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - Flyers‐The Physics of Amorphous Solids, 1983 (Box-folder 35:12)
  - The Physics of Amorphous Solids Correspondence, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 35:13)
  - Permissions for Figures, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 35:14)
  - Percolation Sources, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 35:15)
  - Notes for Book, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 35:16)
  - Glass Transitions, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Mott Transition / Anderson Transition, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Technion Lecturer (Spring 1972), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Bat‐Sheva Lecture Notes, Haifa (January 1975), 1973-1976 (Box-folder 36:4)